[Music]
if you like working with the data
analysis tool in business Central we
have a few new goodies for you they're
actually a bit old because they were
backported to the current version but
they are also available in the 2025
release Wave 1 the first thing is how do
you export to excel you've always been
able to do this but in this release wave
we made it a little bit easier the first
method is simply if you right click in
the data area choose Excel export and
then choose open in Excel and you get
your data in
Excel the other way which is in which is
new is to use the menu here on the data
analysis Tab and simply choose open in
Excel now if you look at the file names
this one
is um a little bit nicer in my opinion
because you also get the file name of
your Excel
workbook uh with a name not not with the
name export but with a name of the page
you're using customer ler entries in
this example and the name of your
analysis tab so if I open here I get my
Excel file or Excel workbook right away